[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript data type?",
        "answer": "True",
        "choice_a": "Number",
        "choice_b": "String",
        "choice_c": "Boolean",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript variable declaration?",
        "answer": "div",
        "choice_a": "var",
        "choice_b": "let",
        "choice_c": "const",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript variable declaration has a global scope?",
        "answer": "var",
        "choice_a": "let",
        "choice_b": "const",
        "choice_c": "function",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript variable declarations has a block scope?",
        "answer": "let",
        "choice_a": "var",
        "choice_b": "function",
        "choice_c": "num",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an increment operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "++",
        "choice_a": "--",
        "choice_b": "//",
        "choice_c": "&&",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a single line comment in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "//",
        "choice_a": "<!--",
        "choice_b": "#",
        "choice_c": "%",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "%%",
        "choice_a": "&&",
        "choice_b": "||",
        "choice_c": "!",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the AND logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "&&",
        "choice_a": "||",
        "choice_b": "!",
        "choice_c": "##",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the OR logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "||",
        "choice_a": "&&",
        "choice_b": "!",
        "choice_c": "**",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the NOT logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "!",
        "choice_a": "&&",
        "choice_b": "||",
        "choice_c": "//",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a correctly defined JavaScript function?",
        "answer": "function myFunction()",
        "choice_a": "function myFunction[]",
        "choice_b": "function myFunction{}",
        "choice_c": "function == myFunction()",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the script?",
        "answer": "<script>",
        "choice_a": "<js>",
        "choice_b": "<javascript>",
        "choice_c": "<body>",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for linking an external JavaScript file?",
        "answer": "<script src=\"xxx.js\">",
        "choice_a": "<script href=\"xxx.js\">",
        "choice_b": "<script alt=\"xxx.js\">",
        "choice_c": "getElement(\"xxx.js\")",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you call a function named myFunction?",
        "answer": "myFunction()",
        "choice_a": "call myFunction()",
        "choice_b": "alert(myFunction)",
        "choice_c": "getElement(myFunction)",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the index number of the first element in a JavaScript array?",
        "answer": "0",
        "choice_a": "1",
        "choice_b": "2",
        "choice_c": "3",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a correct JavaScript array?",
        "answer": "var classmates = [\"Bob\",\"Jane\",\"Mary\"]",
        "choice_a": "var classmates = {\"Bob\",\"Jane\",\"Mary\"}",
        "choice_b": "var classmates = (\"Bob\",\"Jane\",\"Mary\")",
        "choice_c": "var classmates = [1:\"Bob\",2:\"Jane\",3:\"Mary\"]",
        "quiz_id": 1
    }, 
    {
        "question": "How do you return the number of elements in a JavaScript array?",
        "answer": "array.length",
        "choice_a": "array.numberElements",
        "choice_b": "array.getLength",
        "choice_c": "array(totalElements)",
        "quiz_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you allow a user to enter a value that is stored as a string in Python?",
        "answer": "input(\"Enter a value: \")",
        "choice_a": "cin(\"Enter a value: \")",
        "choice_b": "insert(\"Enter a value: \")",
        "choice_c": "prompt(\"Enter a value: \")",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you output \"Hello World\" to the user in Python?",
        "answer": "print(\"Hello World\")",
        "choice_a": "output(\"Hello World\")",
        "choice_b": "display(\"Hello World\")",
        "choice_c": "cout(\"Hello World\")",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Python reserved word?",
        "answer": "local",
        "choice_a": "global",
        "choice_b": "assert",
        "choice_c": "yield",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a single line comment in Python?",
        "answer": "#",
        "choice_a": "<!--",
        "choice_b": "//",
        "choice_c": "%",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the modulo operator in Python?",
        "answer": "%",
        "choice_a": "^",
        "choice_b": "*",
        "choice_c": "#",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you reverse the string \"Hello World\" in Python?",
        "answer": "\"Hello World[::-1]\"",
        "choice_a": "reverse(\"Hello World\")",
        "choice_b": "\"Hello World\".switch",
        "choice_c": "\"Hello World\"(end 0)",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct file etension for Python files?",
        "answer": ".py",
        "choice_a": ".pyth",
        "choice_b": ".pt",
        "choice_c": ".js",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which operator is used to multiply numbers in Python?",
        "answer": "*",
        "choice_a": "x",
        "choice_b": "#",
        "choice_c": "%",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a TUPLE in Python?",
        "answer": "(\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\")",
        "choice_a": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
        "choice_b": "{\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"}",
        "choice_c": "/\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"/",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a SET in Python?",
        "answer": "{\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"}",
        "choice_a": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
        "choice_b": "(\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\")",
        "choice_c": "/\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"/",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a LIST in Python?",
        "answer": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
        "choice_a": "{\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"}",
        "choice_b": "(\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\")",
        "choice_c": "/\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"/",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a DICTIONARY in Python?",
        "answer": "[\"name\": \"apple\", \"color\": \"red\"]",
        "choice_a": "{\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"}",
        "choice_b": "(\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\")",
        "choice_c": "/\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"/",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is unordered and unindexed?",
        "answer": "Set",
        "choice_a": "List",
        "choice_b": "Tuple",
        "choice_c": "Dictionary",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is ordered and unchangeable?",
        "answer": "Tuple",
        "choice_a": "Set",
        "choice_b": "List",
        "choice_c": "Dictionary",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is ordered and changeable?",
        "answer": "List",
        "choice_a": "Set",
        "choice_b": "Tuple",
        "choice_c": "Dictionary",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections stores data in key:value pairs?",
        "answer": "Dictionary",
        "choice_a": "Set",
        "choice_b": "Tuple",
        "choice_c": "List",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the index number of the first element in a Python array?",
        "answer": "0",
        "choice_a": "1",
        "choice_b": "2",
        "choice_c": "3",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing an if statement in Python?",
        "answer": "if x > y:",
        "choice_a": "if x > y then:",
        "choice_b": "if (x > y)",
        "choice_c": "if => x > y",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing a while loop in Python?",
        "answer": "while x > y:",
        "choice_a": "while (x > y)",
        "choice_b": "while x > y {",
        "choice_c": "while => x > y",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing a for loop in Python?",
        "answer": "for x in y:",
        "choice_a": "for x > y",
        "choice_b": "for each x in y",
        "choice_c": "for (x > y)",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statemen is used to stop a loop in Python?",
        "answer": "break",
        "choice_a": "return",
        "choice_b": "stop",
        "choice_c": "exit",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you return the number of elements in a Python list?",
        "answer": "len(listName)",
        "choice_a": "listName.numberElements",
        "choice_b": "listName.length",
        "choice_c": "listName(totalElements)",
        "quiz_id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a method to print an output to the console?",
        "answer": "Console.WriteLine(\"Hello World!\")",
        "choice_a": "console.log(\"Hello World!\")",
        "choice_b": "print(\"Hello World!\")",
        "choice_c": "Console.State(\"Hello World!\")",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a single-line comment?",
        "choice_a": "//",
        "choice_b": "##",
        "choice_c": "**",
        "choice_d": "%%",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a multi-line comment?",
        "choice_a": "/*",
        "choice_b": "//",
        "choice_c":"##",
        "choice_d": "|#",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What keyword do you add to make a variable constant?",
         "const",
         "fixed",
        "constant",
         "static",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an acceptable variable name?",
         "minutesPerHour",
         "5dayForecast",
        "protected",
         "Two+Ten=",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a data type?",
         "true",
         "int",
        "char",
         "long",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum value of a byte?",
         "255",
         "127",
        "32,767",
         "2,147,483,647",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a floating point data type?",
         "double",
         "int",
        "bool",
         "char",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an arithmetic operator?",
         "#",
         "+",
        "%",
         "/",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decrement operator?",
         "--",
         ">",
        "!",
         "^",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the modulus (%) operator do?",
         "Return the division remainder",
         "Divide one value by another",
        "Return the factorial of a number",
         "Decreases the value of a number",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the && logical operator do?",
         "Return true if both statements are true",
         "Returns true if one of the statements is true",
        "Returns the division remainder",
         "Returns false if the result is true",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the || logical operator do?",
         "Returns true if one of the statements is true",
         "Return true if both statements are true",
         "Returns the previous value",
         "Returns false if the result is true",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the ! logical operator do?",
         "Returns false if the result is true",
         "Returns true if one of the statements is true",
         "Return true if both statements are true",
         "Returns the previous value",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the index number of the first element in a C# array?",
         "0",
         "1",
        "-1",
         "2",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
         "break",
         "stop",
        "return",
         "exit",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
         "return",
         "break",
        "get",
         "void",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which access modifier makes the code accessible for all classes?",
         "public",
         "private",
        "open",
         "void",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which access modifier makes the code only acccessible within the same class?",
         "private",
         "public",
        "static",
         "secure",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which access modifier makes the code accessible within the same class, or in a class that is inherited from that class?",
         "protected",
         "private",
        "internal",
         "inherit",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which access modifier makes the code accessible within its own assembly, but not from another assembly?",
         "internal",
         "protected",
        "private",
         "locked",
        "quiz_id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword breaks one iteration of a loop?",
         "continue",
         "break",
        "skip",
         "next",
        "quiz_id": 4
        };
]